Deema says, “Hummy yummy,”
“I feel something in my tummy!”
Deema’s tummy goes rumble, rumble,
Like a little hungry drum.
She wants something tasty, tasty,
“Can I please have some?”
Hummy yummy in my tummy,
Hummy yummy, feed me, Mummy!
Deema’s hungry, time to eat,
Give her something good and sweet!
Hummy yummy in my tummy,
Hummy yummy, feed me, Mummy!
Clap your hands and tap your feet,
Deema says, “It’s time to eat!”
Apples, bananas, berries too,
Carrots make her crunch and chew.
Cheese and toast or rice and peas,
“Something yummy for me, please!”
Hummy yummy in my tummy,
Hummy yummy, feed me, Mummy!
Deema’s hungry, time to eat,
Give her something good and sweet!
Hummy yummy in my tummy,
Hummy yummy, feed me, Mummy!
Clap your hands and tap your feet,
Deema says, “It’s time to eat!”
Mix it, stir it, one, two, three,
Make a yummy plate for Deema.
Nibble, giggle, chew, chew, chew,
Deema shares her snack with you!
Hummy yummy in my tummy,
Now Deema’s tummy feels so happy!
Something healthy, something neat,
Thank you for my yummy treat!
Hummy yummy in my tummy,
No more rumbling in my tummy!
Clap your hands and sing with Deema,
Yummy, yummy—one, two, three!
Deema says, “Hummy yummy,”
“Happy food inside my tummy!”